Guide to the John D. Wirth Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2011-079
  - Fisher [USDA personnel records] (Box 3)
  - Knight [USDA personnel records] (Box 3)
  - Griffin [USDA personnel records] (Box 3)
  - Metzer [USDA personnel records] (Box 3)
  - Hedgcock [USDA personnel records] (Box 3)
  - Associate Committee on Trail Smelter Smoke (Box 3)
  - Canadian Research 1941 and comments on Swain/Dean report (Box 3)
  - Canada on La Paz and later air discussions (Box 3)
  - Plan of Investigation (Box 3)
  - Smelter Fumes Committee (Box 3)
  - Griffin's activities (Box 3)
  - Thomas, WHO issue (Box 3)
  - Southwest Environmental Service [loose papers] (Box 4)
  - Robinson (Box 4)
  - Southwest Environmental Service (Box 4)
  - Howecamp interviews, etc. (Box 4)
  - Metzger interview (Box 4)
  - Kamp interview (Box 4)
  - Priscilla Robinson (Box 4)
  - Dick Kamp interviews (Box 4)
  - Bowerman, Howkamp interviews (Box 4)
  - Scanlon (Box 4)
  - Gov. Babbit interview (Box 4)
  - Lajous/Szekely interview (Box 4)
  - Nancy Wrona interview 4/1/88 (Box 4)
  - Groups Against Smelter Pollution (GASP) (Box 4)
  - Trail Smelter Question [unfoldered photocopies] (Box 4)
  - 1986 Smelter Conference (AZ) (Box 4)
  - German smokegas research (Box 5)
  - German smelters (Box 5)
  - EPA - grass roots (Box 5)
  - Key EPA documents (Box 5)
  - Columbia Valley pollution (Box 5)
  - Trail 3 (Box 5)
  - loose photocopies, etc. (Box 5)
  - Litigation report and attachments, 1986 (Box 5)
  - loose photocopies, etc. (Box 5)
  - A2 [illegible] and state petition and report, 1970s (Box 5)
  - Hearings (Box 5)
  - Appropriation hearings (Box 5)
  - PD general (Box 5)
  - PD documents 7/97 (Box 5)
  - Morenci and Outokumpu (Box 5)
  - Morenci (Box 5)
  - Astarco? (Box 5)
  - Carl Hayden (Box 5)
  - Farmers - Douglas (Box 5)
  - Douglas after shutdown (Box 5)
  - Nacozari (Box 5)
  - Annex IV (Box 5)
  - Health - Douglas (Box 5)
  - Moses suit, 1971-1980 (Box 5)
  - La Caridad, Cananea (add to ms 12/97) (Box 5)
  - Acid rain, west (Box 5)
  - Acid rain, EPA (Box 5)
  - Mexican documents (Box 5)
  - Mexican workers and copper (Box 5)
  - unfoldered clippings, publications, etc. (Box 6)
  - "The Petroleum Industry in Canada Volume I: The Great Oil Age" [draft], Canadian Petroleum Association (Box 6)
  - Ross MacKimmie (Box 6)
  - ERCB and other Alberta archives (formerly Oil and Gas Conservation Board of Alberta) (Box 6)
  - Glenbow archives (Box 6)
  - loose photocopies and reports (Box 6)
  - Norm Chappel (Box 6)
  - W. R. Connole (Box 6)
  - Canadian sects (Hutterites, etc.) (Box 6)
  - Ernest Manning interview (Box 6)
  - Canadian Energy Policy (Box 6)
  - "The Alberta-California Pipeline Project," drafts, 1988-1989 (Box 6)
  - loose reports, etc. (Box 6)
  - PG&E (Box 6)
  - Jack Horton (Box 6)
  - George Govier interview, Two audiocassettes (Box 6)
  - Carl Nickle interview, Two audiocassettes (Box 6)
  - "North Meets South in the West," poster for lecture by Wirth at Colorado State University (Box 6)
  - unfoldered news clippings, publications, photocopies (Box 7)
General note
The collection is unprocessed. A preliminary inventory for part of it is available; please consult the University Archivist for further assistance.